showingsuite.com 2015-12-07

# Privacy Policy | Showing Suite Real Estate SoftwareShowing Suite

## Last modified: March 25, 2009

## Introduction

Showing Suite, Inc. respects each individual’s right to personal privacy. This Policy applies to all the products, services, and websites offered by Showing Suite, Inc. We will collect and use information through our websites only in the ways disclosed in this statement. This statement applies solely to information collected at Showing Suite, Inc.’s websites. 

## Part I. Information Collection

Showing Suite, Inc. collects information through our website at several points. We collect the following information about primary visitors: including their names, company names, phone numbers, fax numbers, addresses and email addresses.We may also collect names, company names, phone numbers, fax numbers, addresses and email addresses which our users divulge about other individuals, such as other real estate agents, prospects or clients. Showing Suite, Inc. does not actively market to children, and we never knowingly ask a child under 13 to divulge personal information.We collect the following general data that is not personally identifiable information. Real estate prices, characteristics and days in the Showing Suite, Inc. system. We collect demographic data in order to increase the feedback response service for our subscribers. 

We verify the accuracy of this information by the users of the Showing Suite, Inc. system. We collect this information through registration forms, click stream tracking, automatic logging files, and so on. This information will include name, company name, phone numbers, email address, etc. The information is collected voluntarily per our user agreement. To receive our products and services, this information is mandatory in order to use the software as it was intended. Other information we request is optional.

We do employ cookies. A cookie is a small text file that our Web server places on a user’s computer hard drive to be a unique identifier. Cookies enable Showing Suite, Inc. to track usage patterns and deliver customized content to users. Our cookies do not have an expiration date. Our cookies do not collect personally identifiable information. Showing Suite, Inc. lets other companies that show advertisements on some of our pages set and access their cookies on your computer. Other companies’ use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one. Advertisers or other companies do not have access to Showing Suite, Inc.’s cookies.

“Third-Party Web Beacons: We use third-party web beacons from Google to help analyze where visitors go and what they do while visiting our website. Google may also use anonymous information about your visits to this and other websites in order to improve its products and services and provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice used by Google, click here.”  

## Part II. Information Usage

The information collected by Showing Suite, Inc. will be used for software and service upgrade specific purposes. Users who provide information will receive access to the Showing Suite, Inc.. system, and may periodically receive emails from us (educational, system update notifications, etc).Registered users will receive additional announcements from us about products, services, special deals, and a newsletter. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to not receive these types of communications.The information we collect will be used to create customer profiles based on browsing or purchasing history. We will not supplement information collected at our website with data from other sources. 

Your credit card information is passed directly to our Credit Card Payment Gateway to process your periodic charges. These third parties will use the information as follows: information needed for payment purposes only.

We offer links to other websites. Please note: When you click on links to other Web sites, we encourage you to read their privacy policies. Their standards may differ from ours. Our website may offer chats, forums or message boards. Please be advised that information posted in these venues becomes public knowledge.  
If our policy on information collection or uses changes, the updated version will be posted on our website.

## Part III. Access to Information

Showing Suite, Inc. maintains the accuracy of our information by users entering their own information. Users may access their own personal information and correct any inaccuracies they may find by logging into their account & updating their profile. Users may delete their information from our database by terminating their account. 

## Part IV. Problem Resolution

If problems arise; users may contact Showing Suite, Inc. by sending an email to support@showingsuite.com or by writing to Showing Suite, Inc., 4901 Morena Blvd, Suite 207, San Diego, CA 92117. We are committed to resolving disputes within 24-48 hours of notification. 

## Part V. Data Storage and Security

Showing Suite, Inc. protect user information with the following security measures: We use security measures such as encryption, security protocols, fire walls, SSL encryption and other technology to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of data used by our system. 

If this privacy policy changes in the future, all account holders will be notified of the change at least ten (10) days before it occurs and have the option to terminate his or her account and thus have their data removed from the system.
